rudraksha-ratna.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy - Rudraksha Ratna | Rudraksha Ratna

Rudraksha-Ratna.com is an online e-commerce designed to provide an easy way for our members to shop online. Rudraksha-Ratna.com members create their own unique profile using our predetermined form. Name, address, telephone and email id is required information to become a member. We also collect credit card information and IP address once the member transacts on Rudraksha-Ratna.com. None of the information we gather can be used by the public (visitors, other members, and anyone not employed by Rudraksha-Ratna.com, its corporate affiliates, or the financial institutions we use to process membership charges) to identify a specific individual.

**Service Providers:** We use other third parties to provide logistics and payment processing on our site. When you transact or place an order on our site, we will share shipping address with the logistics provider and credit card number with the payment gateway provider as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

We do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your private information without your permission except to the financial institution that processes your credit card transactions. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

Rudraksha-Ratna.com uses cookies to provide the services, to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit different pages on our site, and for other purposes. Please note that cookies are used only to recollect information sent to your computer from Rudraksha-Ratna.com. We CANNOT access any information not sent by Rudraksha-Ratna.com. We also do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

**Third Party Cookies:** Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Rudraksha-Ratna.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Rudraksha-Ratna.com sends email offers to individuals who would require information on product updates and services. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
